[music]
>> Detroit welcomed in NFC North foe Green
Bay for a Thanksgiving Day classic. Now
the Motor City will go home and eat
their turkey legs covered in tears.
Lions fall to the Packers 31 to 24.
Welcome to the Detroit Lions Live
postgame show presented by Keer Auto
Insurance. Alongside the Super Bowl
champ, Lomas Brown, and Hall of Fame
semifinalist
>> Thank you.
>> I'm Dani Rogers. Thanks so much for
spending some of your Thanksgiving Day
holiday with us. It all came down to the
fourth quarter for Detroit. Multiple
opportunities to either tie this ball
game or put it away. The offense fell
short on a fourth down drop from Jamo,
and then Jared Goff takes a sack, and it
didn't look pretty out there for him in
the pocket.
>> No, Danny, didn't. Unfortunately, it
didn't look pretty pretty much most of
the game. I mean, you have to give Green
Bay a lot of credit. They came in with a
certain game plan that they wanted to
execute against the Lions, and they
executed it. They really did. And Danny,
I'm telling you, what's disturbing to me
a second week in a row is that we can't
generate pressure on quarterbacks
opposing quarterbacks. And if you give a
quarterback any type of time, that's
what's going to happen. They're going to
sustain drives. They're going to hit
their guys. They're going to make
explosive plays against us. Give Jordan
Love, Matt LaFleur, and that Green Bay
Packers team, Michael Parsons, and the
rest of the guys a lot of credit. They
came in and took the victory from us. To
your point, Detroit had no sacks on
Jordan Love and the Green Bay Packers
offense. Some bright spots here. Okay,
hear me out, LB.
>> Okay. This is one of the best third down
performances we've seen from Detroit
this season. Eight of 13. They were 0
for 2 on fourth down. Those were some
daggers. Despite Detroit leading time of
possession and not turning the ball
over, they just just could not come up
with those big plays when they needed
it. Big story of the night, the
offensive line is banged up. Center
Graham Glasgow was out of this one with
a knee injury. In steps Tristan Colon, a
free agent acquisition. That line didn't
look like it could hold up for most of
the part. There were bright spots, but a
few times they let that pressure get to
Jared Goff.
>> No, you're absolutely right. And the
thing you have to have, especially in
the NFL, you have to have continuity.
And Danny, when you guys don't practice,
you can't get that chemistry down. And
it's hard coming to a game and having to
execute when you have guys in and out
the lineup. And unfortunately, that's
been the case for most of the year with
our offensive line. You know, we've had
different starters there. And you know,
we've had like you said, not having
Graham Glasgow there today. So is is
this been tough? And I know it's been
tough trying to put a game plan
together. But you know, we're going to
have to overcome that. Those are things
that you go through throughout the NFL
season. You just have to find a way to
overcome it.
>> Detroit couldn't find their way in the
run game like we've been accustomed to.
Running back Jahmyr Gibbs ran went off
for 219 rushing yards last week. This
week he was bottled up by that Packers
run D. 68 yards on the ground. David
Montgomery, when this team needed some
more knuckles and not as much Sonic,
Montgomery delivered the boom including
that second quarter touchdown out of the
wildcat formation. Bullied his way into
the end zone to put Detroit within
three. No, you're right. And
David's again, we talked about it.
Jahmyr, yeah, he had the big game last
week. But you're going to need David
Montgomery. You you're going to need
both of those guys. They compliment each
other so so very well. So you're going
to need David. I thought David was
you're right. He did picked up some
timely third downs for us. Like you
said, when we needed him to get in in
the end zone, he was the one that got in
the end zone for us. But again, when you
talk about 3.4 yards per carry, you
know, that's just that average just
isn't good enough to sustain the run
game. So again, we talk about being able
to sustain that, pick up first downs,
keep the drive going, keep their offense
on the sideline, our offense out there
on the field. We just weren't able to do
that consistently today, Danny. Detroit
has taken some injuries to their pass
catchers including tight end Sam
LaPorta, which is not new news. He is
out indefinitely, but his counterpart,
tight end Brock Wright, was also out
today as as well as Kalif Raymond, punt
returner, kick returner, and wide
receiver. And then Amon-Ra St. Brown,
the leading receiver for Detroit, goes
down in the first quarter. These two
stepped up big time including Isaac
TeSlaa with one score here, and then Tom
Kennedy just kept churning out the big
plays today.
>> You're right. I'm proud of Tom Kennedy.
And plus he had double duty, right? He
was our return guy on punts and our
return guy in the kickoff return game.
But Danny, we're going to have to rely
on these guys to step up even more. I
hate to say that. Jamo had a big game
today, but he's going to have to have
somebody else that compliments him. Tom
Kennedy, I thought did a great job of
finding the soft spots in the Green Bay
defense, sitting it down. Big 23-yard
reception early in the game that helped
Jared Goff out. But we're going to need
more from these guys. And I think Dan
Campbell is probably going to have to
put more on their plates. Bright spot
bright spot for Detroit today. And the
reason why we can all go home and eat
some pumpkin pie, some apple pie, pecan
pie, whatever you love. It's because of
this man right here, wide receiver
Jameson Williams. In the 2-minute drill
before the half, came up with a quick
third and three quick pitch from Goff.
Pranced into the end zone for the score.
He is lethal on the run, and that's
exactly how you want him every single
play.
>> You're exactly right. And the thing that
I love is Jared with his accuracy. He
gives Jamo a opportunity to catch the
ball and get that yards after the catch.
And that's so important, especially when
we run a lot of drag routes. We run a
lot of slot
slant routes. We like to take the take
advantage of the middle of the defense.
I think Jamo's has done his best work
coming across the middle of the
defenses, catching the ball on the run,
and using that outstanding speed. So
again, talk about putting more and more
on guys' plates. I know a lot more is
going to have to go on Jamo, and he's
going to have to produce for us. Jameson
Williams led Detroit's receivers today.
We see him inconsistently throughout the
weeks. Is he continuing to make his case
to move up higher in the progression
chart for Jared Goff?
>> I mean, and that comes from the
quarterback having confidence in A,
knowing whether a wide receiver is going
to be at. He's if he's supposed to be at
10 yards, he's going to be at 10 yards.
But B, making the catches. You have to
be able to make those crucial crucial
catches. Jamo, he's been doing that. And
and like I said, Jared's going to have
to rely on him. He doesn't have his
blanket in Sam LaPorta. So it's a lot of
guys that he's probably unfamiliar with,
hadn't worked a lot with, that he's
going to have to become more and more
familiar with, build that chemistry with
these guys sooner than later since our
turnaround is so short next week. Mhm.
Back here next Thursday against the
Dallas Cowboys. Let's look at this
Detroit Lions defense. Two of the top
guys that continue to lock down,
especially the run game, held Packers to
125 yards rushing, right about their
average. Jack Campbell, Alex Anzalone,
those two combined, no matter where you
put them on the field, they're making an
impact, Lomas. Yeah, and not just in
tackling, too, in coverage. I mean,
these guys have to cover the running
backs. They have to cover the tight
ends. And I think they've been doing a
nice job. Look, we've been leaning on
our linebacking group most of this year,
especially on the defensive side of the
ball. They've been doing a nice job. Um
they're continuing to lead our defense.
So Danny, we're going to have to lean
more and more on these guys. Again, I
talk about the responsibilities that
they have to take on. They're just going
to have to take on even more, especially
with some of the injury problems we have
in our secondary. You know, and guys
going in and out. You rely on these
linebackers A, to get guys lined up
where they need to be. But B, be able to
make the tackle or cover guys that they
need to cover. Speaking of the
secondary, safety Brian Branch continues
to step up while his counterpart, Kerby
Joseph, is out with injury right now.
And Branch was all over the field. Led
Detroit in tackles, 10 total, two passes
defended. He delivered the boom here
today. And he's a reason why this
Detroit's defense can put can keep this
team, you know, giving this team a
a chance to win, rather.
>> Yeah, I thought BB was big today. Like
you said, not only with coming up and
supporting the run and making
sure-handed tackles, but defending the
pass, too. I thought he had sticky
coverage on the guys that he had to
defend. I thought he was huge in this
game. I thought he was a reason why the
defense played as well as they played
today. Again, we're going to need him
more and more.
Um hopefully he can get his running
partner back in Kerby Joseph, but it's
just been tough, man. Calvin Shepherd, I
keep talking about the job that he has
done, especially when you have so many
moving parts on your defense because of
injury. I think he's done an outstanding
job of getting these guys where they
need to be at and putting them in a
position to have success. Back-to-back
weeks for Detroit's defense. We've seen
a handful of explosive passes being
given up including on that final drive
from Green Bay. Detroit had a chance to
give the ball back to their offense.
They couldn't step up. Where are you
seeing the disconnect on that side?
>> We have to get pressure on the
quarterback. I'm I'm going to harp on
this. I'm going to beat the drum on this
all day long. If you let a NFL
quarterback get comfortable in the game,
you're going to have a hard time
stopping them. One hit, I mean, we had
to affect Jordan Love a lot more than we
did today. You know, his uniform was
clean. I don't even know if they have to
wash his uniform, Dan. And that's
disturbing because last week it happened
to us with Jameson Winston. So, again,
we're going to have to get better. I
don't know how we do that. I don't know
if Calvin Shepard's going to have to
send more guys. I don't know what we're
going to have to do, but we got to
affect these quarterbacks more and more
early in the game to get them
uncomfortable.
>> Urgency has got to be a keyword here
going forward for Detroit. Head coach
Dan Campbell is standing by the podium.
Let's hear from him.
Okay.
Credit that team
and Matt. You know, they did a good job,
man. They closed that game out and uh
you know, they they made the critical
plays.
You know, proud of the way our guys
fought. You know, I feel like um
came in ready to go from that aspect and
um
certainly plenty of energy, but it
really this game came down to fourth
down and those critical moments and we
were 0 for 2 and they were able to
capitalize on three of them. So, you
know, and those are the those are the
one or two
plays really that make the difference uh
when you're playing a really good team.
So,
um
that's really kind of what it came down
to.
So, like I told the team, it's
frustrating, I know. We got a lot to be
thankful for even after a loss.
Um
you know,
um
and look, we dug ourselves a little bit
of a hole. That's that's the bottom
line. We're we are in a little bit of a
hole. Um
but that's just what it is. That's
uh there's nothing more than that. So,
all we got to do is worry about cleaning
up this and then getting to the next
game and finding a way to win the the
next one in front of us. That that will
be after this uh day or two here they
get off. That that's what the focus will
be.
Coach, on the the fourth downs, um you
guys have gone a few games now without
converting one. Is there
something that
is happening on some of those
did early on and then Green Bay's
decision on that last one just to go for
it, you know, playing for the win, I
guess. Yeah, it was a good decision. I
mean, just, you know,
going for the win, finish the game, man.
And they uh you know, they came up with
it. Uh
you know, I thought look, BB was in
phase, man. That was sticky coverage and
um you know, 13 went up, made a hell of
a play, you know. So,
credit to them.
Um
but it wasn't like we weren't in
position.
Uh that's that's just that those are
those moments, you know. Um
But I don't No, I don't look at it.
Uh look, one of those I didn't like one
of those those fourth down calls, you
know.
It felt like um
you know, I I don't know how good of an
opportunity we really gave our guys on
that first one, you know. Um
but
but you know, we we had an opportunity
and and uh
even at the end of the day we had an
opportunity and we we couldn't you know,
we just couldn't get it done there later
in the game. So,
Does that change your approach at all
with the
the struggles you guys have had
No, I mean, it's it's still if it you
know, if you
it a lot of it depends on where the game
is at, too, man. Where the game's at,
the opponent, uh how your defense is
playing,
you know, what do you feel like you have
a real good handle on what you're going
to get from that defense? Uh
you know, who you're going to, all those
things. And so,
um
you know, going into it we liked those
plays. Um
so, no, I I wouldn't say necessarily
that that that's going to have an effect
on me, you know. You always want to
convert them and we've had a lot of
conversions here. It just didn't work
out today. Yeah, you lose Saint 9
minutes into the game. He's probably a
big part of this game plan. You're
already without the lead. You just
talked about needing somebody to step up
and came up.
Who did that for you? Tom had some some
good catches there down the seam. Just
you guys stepped up. I know you fell
short, but you had to probably be proud
of the way some of those guys stepped up
and played out there.
>> for sure. And yeah, when you lose a guy
like Saint, that's it's it's tough. I
mean, he's
there's there's so many things that he
brings to our offense. Everybody knows
the production and the versatility he
has, but also all the dirty work he does
in the run game and all the little
things, man. The nuances of where you
line up to where you go, to who you
block. If it's this look to now if they
go here, you need to slide back to do
that. I mean, he he's so freaking smart,
man.
And he's tough. And so, there's there's
a million jobs he does uh and he does
them at a high that it does it's it it
hurts when you lose him. So,
you know, he and LaPorta were kind of
those guys for us. And when you lose
those guys and then Leaf's the next one,
you know, it becomes difficult. But with
that,
a guy like Jamo stepped up, you know.
And I thought he was electric, made a
lot of big plays for us, you know. Um
that was good to see.
Um and we thought he would, you know,
get it in his hands. I wish he could
have gotten his hands more. We had some
calls there that that you know, the
defense took him away. And so, it had to
go somewhere else, but um he did a good
job. TK, we we trust TK. That's why he's
here. That's why he's on the vet squad
and we elevated him because he he can
return for us, which he did. And he can
do a million jobs on offense. Tesla made
some big plays uh today.
So, that that is a positive. We had
three really new tight ends.
Uh now, Zylstra's played for us, but
Zylstra kind of started for us.
Obviously, we used Skip and then there
was Furk and Hort uh Horton.
>> [snorts]
>> So, um and it was good to see those guys
go compete, mix it up.
How do you feel like the the pass rush
has struggled to to make impact plays so
consistently over the last couple games?
Yeah, I don't I don't know. I don't
know, you know. It's a good question. I
mean, I I need to until I watch this
game, I I I want to know what this game
looks like uh before I make a comment on
that, you know.
Um
so, I'm not sure.
The outlook on Saint Brown, any idea?
Well, I'll know more tomorrow. I I I
don't feel like this is long, long-term.
You know, so that's the good news, but
that doesn't mean it won't be here for,
you know, could be a week or two.
Maybe, if we're lucky. So, you mentioned
dug a hole. How difficult if he's out
and other guys have been injured,
how do you see your way out of this
hole? Well, I guess what I'm saying is
this. You know, just know what kind of
where we're at with the division, you
know, and
um is more of that you need a little
help. You got to do your job. You got to
win and you need a little help. And uh
that that's what it is, but it all
starts with you doing your job and which
is us and and finding a way to win
the next one in front of us. That it
really is that simple. Don't make more
of it needs be. Um
it's frustrating. It sucks. It's tough,
but we've done it we did it to
ourselves. And we're the only ones who
are going to get out of it as well.
So, the news of Frank Ragnow obviously
going forward, how much are you looking
forward to adding him to the mix and
just your reaction to him? Yeah, I'm
fired up, you know, fired up to get to
get Frank uh
to get him back. Um
you know, he wants to play. He wants to
be a part of it. Uh he misses the game.
He misses his teammates. And
um so, we're really fired up, man. He he
brings uh
he's a good football player. He brings a
good football player, a lot of
production back to that old line and and
the game itself. But he's also a great
teammate, man. He was one of our
captains. Um
so, he brings a lot to our team. Can you
explain how that that all came about? A
couple weeks ago it sounded like, you
know,
you know, thinking that wasn't going to
Yeah, it just I I think this is
something that's been on his mind for a
while. And um
you know, and then
and then he called me.
So, we we were good.
What's that?
>> When did he call you in the midst of
this process? Um well, the yesterday
morning is when I got the call
officially. Now, I know there was other
things and look, his teammates have
talked to him, you know. I know some of
those guys have been uh back and forth
with him.
And I got wind of something, you know,
not too long ago.
Um
but hey, man, we're fired up. On the
topic of
sorry. On the topic of the O line, I
know you're not going to make excuses,
but but how difficult has it been to get
into a rhythm with the injuries up
front, with the youth up front? And and
how detrimental has it been to try to
find that rhythm this season? Well,
yeah, I mean, it look it it it just
things are a little different. That's
all. There's just it's just a little
different. That's the best way to say
it. So, sometimes you got to go about
things a little differently. And I
thought those guys battled up there
today, man. You know, I I thought they
um I thought they did some good things
in the run game. I did think we had some
pretty good protection.
Um a lot of our play pass stuff. Now,
you know, I know we got to hit on some
stuff, but but those guys went in there
and competed. Colon started for us at
center, man. I
you know, I thought he was clear. I
thought communication was good. Uh tried
to finish.
You know, so
um
but but there's more to it than that,
too. When things don't go right, it's
it's all encompassing, man. I'm part of
that. All right? I I I can always be
better and need to be better.
Um but it really is. It's all the
positions. It's not just O line. So,
um and and that's what it's that's what
it's all about in finding our own
rhythm, man. And once we find the
rhythm, keep the rhythm. And
uh you just got to go about it a certain
way.
Coach, Dave and John. Talk about urgency
on that that last drive. Six minute
drive.
>> I know. I know that's frustrating when
you're a fan watching, but we
I know how we needed to play against
that defensive front. All right, and
and it was about playing for the last
possession. We were going to do that or
I was going to defense was going to get
the stop. We were going to use our
timeouts, get one more shot to go win
the game, and that's that's how we were
playing it. I wanted to play it just
like that. So,
uh I wanted to keep it in our hands,
uh
and not turn it into a pin your ears
back and start flying up the field with
Micah Parsons and those guys.
Sean, last question.
Dan, where do you where do you think you
are with the your feel of the the flow
of calling plays and it Well, I can
always be better. I mean, there's all
you know, I can always be better.
Um
but
you know, look, I'm I'm always going to
want more. I'm always going to feel like
I need to do some things a little bit
different, but you can always go
hindsight on all this. Well, man, why
don't you run it here? You should have
you know, we should I wish I would have
play pass on this or I'll play I wish I
would have dropped back on this one.
Well,
um
you know,
so
but ultimately look, we didn't win the
game.
Um but as far as the way that I wanted
to play that game offensively, it's that
was the vision I had for it. We just
we got to convert, man. Those first two
series that we had, we got to find a way
to convert on third.
Uh and then the fourth downs, you know.
So, you're talking about two or three
plays ultimately against a good team in
that moment that that made the
difference. One thing without St. Brown,
aren't your fourth down even at third
down options a little bit limited? Is
that where you have to adjust somewhat?
>> Yeah, I mean, look, it's certainly he's
such a Yeah, I mean, he he's a
playmaker, you know, and he does a ton
for us. And so, yeah, I mean, I don't I
certainly don't want to say that it
doesn't influence you or affect you, but
yet
I do have a lot of trust in Tom Kennedy.
I do have a lot of trust in Jamo,
especially when we know what the
coverage is and we got him running. Uh
we still got Gibbs.
Um and so, man, if you like the players
and you like the play, there'll be
sometimes you may not like the coverages
you think you may get or if it's you
know the ball's going to go to this this
player and it's this route that you're
going to have to win on. Maybe you don't
like it, but um
you know,
I in the moment it felt like the right
thing to do
today.
Thanks, Dan.
Guys, your prior success has put you at
the top of the power [music] rankings
list. That's a good thing, right? Well,
just means you've gone from the underdog
to the favorite.
But those expectations come from prior
success, so that's okay. What about
Cure? Where do you guys rank on the
power list? Actually, we just got named
by Forbes as one of the best car
insurance companies in America. Now
you're the favorite. Guess we have a lot
in [music] common.
Go Cure. Go Lions.
Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance.
Log on to cure.com to see how you can
save.
Quarterback Jared Goff looked Micah
Parsons, defensive end for the Green Bay
Packers, in the eyes about 10 times
today. That's the amount of pressures
Parsons was able to have on Goff and two
and a half sacks coming from him alone.
Three sacks on the day against Goff
forced him off his spot, but when Goff
did have time in the pocket, he was
throwing some darts to his wide
receivers. Oh, I'm I mean, 132
quarterback rating. I mean, he did
everything he could to try to keep this
team in this game.
Uh I thought Jared was calm out there
even under pressure. I thought he made
the right reads. He made the right
throws when he needed to do that. So,
you can't really look at your
quarterback on this one. You have to
just kind of look at everything else
that happened. Plus, when you lose your
best receiver, one of your best
offensive weapons through in the game, I
mean, it kind of changes the game plan a
little bit. So, I give Jared a lot of
credit for what he was able to do out
here today.
And Goff will get a reinforcement back.
We just heard from head coach Dan
Campbell. He confirmed center Frank
Ragnow will be back in the fold. No idea
when he'll be in football shape, but
Ragnow will be a pretty big addition
>> That's all right, Dani. I'll take a 70%
Frank Ragnow over anybody else. He is
the guy. I'm telling you, that's
probably been the key to where our
offensive line has kind of been up and
down this year. It's one person, Frank
Ragnow, our center, the quarterback of
the offensive line. To get him back, I
think that just has to be a big boost. I
know it's a big boost to the offensive
line, but to the rest of the guys in
that locker room cuz he was a leader.
So, you get one of your guys back. It
has to pep you up, give you some
confidence that, "Hey, right now we're
in the hole, but we get one of our
leaders back, we can make a run at this
thing towards the end of this season."
Four-time Pro Bowler Ragnow going to
help try to help these Detroit Lions
climb out of that hole. Quarterback
Jared Goff is standing by the podium.
Let's hear from him.
Just to start things off, we just talked
to Dan about Frank coming back. When did
you uh catch wind that he was
considering coming out of retirement? Uh
yeah, a few weeks ago. Um he reached out
and had a little interest, I think, and
got that itch again, and um yeah, we'll
be excited to get him back. Now, how do
you feel like you guys settled in today
after those first couple drives? Um
pretty good, yeah. I thought there was
there was good moments offensively.
Moved the ball
pretty well at times. Obviously wasn't
enough, and
come up short that way. It sucks. It
hurts. Um you know, you wish you had uh
you know, another chance to kind of try
to get another one, but um yeah, man, it
hurts. It sucks. And uh
they played well. You tip your cap.
You lose St. Brown 9 minutes into the
game. Obviously that that's a big loss
already without you.
Just talk about
Jameson stepping up big.
>> Yeah.
Zylstra made some key blocks. Kind of
knew it would become uh Jamo's game
there.
Uh
really before the game, and then when
that happens, you really know it. Um
And then Zylstra, I thought stepped up
and did a good job. I thought TK, he
he's
going to be an unsung hero there being
able to step in and know all the stuff,
and
uh really impressive, but yeah, it's
still a
um yeah, I guess
moral victory that that we were able to
get Jamo going like that.
Different twist for you guys. Green Bay
got the fourth downs that they needed,
and you guys didn't get the fourth down
that you needed.
>> Yeah.
Did Did you like those calls that were
called?
>> Yeah. I did. Um
I got to connect with Jamo there on the
one down the red zone. That's um
I got to give him a better throw, and he
makes the catch. He might score right
there, and then the drive might be over.
Um
that's the one that'll um hurt me for a
while, and
uh and then yeah, they they converted on
their fourth downs, and tip your cap. I
thought they played really well.
How do you guys improve like work on
that and you know, fourth down managing
those? I mean, it's it's been something
you struggled with the last couple
games, but as a team, how do you get
better at converting? I don't think
there's anything you can do to like
you just got to execute in those big
moments. That's really it is. I I I
wish, you know, there was some magic
potion to take to be better on fourth
down, but
there's not. I mean,
dude, I had Jamo open. He's screaming
across. Like, I got to hit him. Like,
that's bottom line. There's no other um
way to fix it. Yeah, I hit him there,
then we're one for two on fourth down,
and
probably get more points there.
Outside of fourth down, you referred to
St. Brown and LaPorta as safety blankets
out there. Just what is it like to be
out there without them? Yeah, I thought
that I thought everyone stepped up and
did a good job, and um Jamo became you
know, that guy that, you know, was
getting open a lot and trying to get him
the ball, and I thought Zylstra did a
good job. And like I said, TK, Ferentz
did a good job. Um yeah, guys stepped
up. Dan talked about
yourself kind of in a hole now just with
where you're at at 7 and 5. Obviously a
different situation where you were last
last year. Just what's the mindset now
at at 7 and 5? Is it still just it's got
to be every week, next opponent?
>> yeah. Win the next one.
Find a way to win the next one, get to 8
and 5.
And then after that, it's going to be
the same answer. So, yeah, we we we we
know where we're at. We certainly know
that this was
uh consequential for division
um rankings and whatnot, but yeah, we
got to win the next one and and find a
way to beat Dallas. If St. Brown is out
for a little bit, at least, how much
does that change what you guys are going
to have to try to do offensively? Uh it
changed some stuff. He's obviously such
a big part of our offense, and um a lot
of it goes through him, so
change a little bit, but not much.
Beyond this game, there was news
yesterday of Frank coming back. You two
have played a lot of football together.
Um when did you get the news, and and
how do you feel about it?
>> few weeks um
I I mean, I didn't know he was coming
back for sure a few weeks ago, but I
knew he was interested a few weeks ago,
and
yeah, I'm glad he's back. It'll be fun.
Um
uh yeah, I don't know when he'll end up
playing, but I'm sure he'll be back
soon.
Thank you, guys. Thanks, guys.
Guys, your prior success has put you at
the top of the power rankings [music]
list. That's a good thing, right? Well,
just means you've gone from the underdog
to the favorite.
But those expectations come from prior
[music] success, so that's okay.
What about Cure? Where do you guys rank
on the power Actually, we just got named
by Forbes as one of the best car
insurance companies in America.
>> [music]
>> Now you're the favorite. Guess we have a
lot in common.
Go Cure. Go Lions.
Cure Auto Insurance. Drive well.
Detroit Lions Live is brought to you by
Cure Auto Insurance.
Log on to cure.com to see how you can
save.
Detroit has 1 week to figure this thing
out. They return home to take on the
Dallas Cowboys who are currently facing
the Kansas City Chiefs in Arlington. 7
to 7 is the score right now in the first
quarter. Dak Prescott, the Cowboys,
they're putting something together,
trying to get their hopes up of getting
into the playoffs. Where is the biggest
threat in this matchup? Well, Dani,
you're right. You talk about that Dak
Prescott and that offense coming in here
where they fortified that defense, too,
bringing in Quinton Williams and
another linebacker that they brought in
the kind of fortified the middle of that
that defensive front. So, you know, not
only on the offensive side we're going
to have to have some of our best our
best game, but on the defensive side too
cuz that's an explosive offense when you
talk about CD Lamb and some of the
weapons that Dak Prescott has. So, it's
going to be a tall task and depends on
what happened today. We know we're going
to find out a lot about what we need to
happen as far as us in the postseason. I
know I'm looking ahead cuz we got to
take it one game at a time and the only
the next game is the Dallas game, but
Danny you have to be looking ahead or
looking at the big picture just to know
where you are. No off days for this
Detroit Lions offensive line especially
going up against the Cowboys defensive
front. Reminder, wear white everyone
next Thursday 8:15 kickoff. Do the exact
opposite of what I'm doing right now.
Wear white. [laughter] Don't wear black.
You'll stick out like a sore thumb. I
don't know the last time I've seen a
whiteout at Ford Field. And I'm pumped
for it.
>> well, today they had the white towels
the rally towels going today. They were
white today. So, that looked so good.
So, imagine everybody in white in here.
It could be a little advantage for us.
We're going to need every advantage we
can get today. This channel the Penn
State whiteout energy. That's that's
what we need here inside Ford Field. All
right, final takeaways from this game
Lomas. If the playoffs started today for
Detroit, the Lions are out. They're in
the eighth spot. Only the top seven
teams from each conference make it in.
So, where do you look at this Detroit
Lions defense and where do you put the
bandage at to get things going again?
So, the first thing and I know it's
obvious. Try to get healthy. We got to
try to get some of our guys back. When
you talk about missing Brock Wright
today. Now Amon-Ra's out. Kalif was out.
You know, we had to think about Graham
Glasgow. We had a lot of guys missing
today. So, that's the number one thing
we have to try to get healthy. But
Danny, we got to find a way to affect
these quarterbacks that come in here cuz
think about some of the quarterbacks we
got coming in here the rest of the
season. So, Calvin Shepherd's going to
have to go back to the drawing board and
figure out a way for us to affect these
quarterbacks coming here. And we're just
going to have to continue on offense to
try to execute, get first downs, keep
the ball moving, try to keep those good
quarterbacks on the sideline, and try to
get the ball in the end zone. That's I
know I'm saying a lot and I know it's a
tall task, but that's what we're going
to have to start with and that's what
we're going to have to try to accomplish
over these next few weeks. Next 7 days
are crucial for Detroit who falls to 7
and 5 on the season after a loss on
Thanksgiving Day here in the Motor City.
For Lomas Brown, I'm Dani Rogers. Thanks
so much for tuning into the Detroit what
do
Happy Thanksgiving. I'm thankful for you
Lomas. I never want you to think that
I'm not.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you for shouting that out. Thanks
so much for tuning in. 31 to 24 is the
final from Ford Field. We'll see you
right back here next week.